Guide to the New York Metro Area Postal Union Photographs PHOTOS.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series XIV: Demonstrations/Rallies, VII (Box 2)
  - Demonstration supporting HR 13000 (US Aid Bill) Raises for postal employees, Washington, DC- 1969
  - Pay Raise Demo- General Post Office- 1970
  - Strike- 1970
  - Pay Raise Rally- New York City, undated
- Series XV: Signs/Billboards, VIII (Box 3)
  - Union Sign- 1960
  - Billboards- 1962
  - Pony Express sign on wall of Union building- 1961
  - Horse and Buggy Leg Sign, undated
  - APWU Posters, undated
- Series XVI: Elections, IX (Box 3)
  - Employees rep election- 1962
  - Employees rep election- 1957
  - M-H Election- 1964
  - Mail Handler election, Morgan Station- 1967
- Series XVII: Contracts, X (Box 3)
  - First contract negotiations, Manhattan and Bronx- 1963
  - First contract Adoption, undated
  - MH contract signing- 1968
- Series XVIII: Dinners/Parties, XI (Box 3)
  - Annual Children's Christmas Party- 1957
  - Christmas/ Chanukah Party- 1957
  - Christmas/ Chanukah Party- 1958
  - Christmas/ Chanukah Party- 1959
  - Christmas/ Chanukah Party- 1960
  - Open House Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union- 6/ 1961, Jun 1961
  - Annual Delegates Dinner- 1961
  - Installation Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union- 1961
  - Installation Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union- 1962
  - Delegates Dinner- 1962
  - Delegates Dinner, Diplomat Hotel- 1/1963, Jan 1963
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, undated
  - Delegates Dinner- 1/9/1964, Jan 9, 1964
  - Lincoln Day Dinner- 1964
  - Cocktail Party- 10/21/1964, Oct 21, 1964
  - Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union Installation- 1964
  - Dinner Honoring Cong Ryan- 1964, May 17, 1905
  - Annual Elardo Award Dinner- 1965
  - Congressional Breakfast- 1965, May 18, 1905
  - Open House- New Office- 1/1968, Jan 1968
  - Inauguration Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union officers- 1968
  - M Biller, JFK Libraries (Luncheon) Presentation- 1968
  - Delegates Dinner, Awards- 1/1969, Jan 1969
  - Biller Testimonial- 1969
  - B Schwartz Photos NPU Open House, 10th Anniversary NPU- 1969
  - Delegates Dinner- 1970
  - Elardo Delegates Dinner- 1972
  - Annual Dinner, undated
  - Children's Party [per-1959?], undated
  - H Kamish Retirement, undated
- Series XIX: Award Ceremonies, XII (Box 3)
  - Membership Prize Winners- 11/1959, 12/1959, Nov 1959 - Dec 1959
  - Presentation of Scroll by Joint Conference to David Silvergleid- 1/1960, Jan 1960
  - Membership Prize Winners- 2/17/1960, Feb 17, 1960
  - Cong Addabbo receiving Elardo Award- 1963
  - Scholarship Award- 1964
  - Elardo Dinner- 1964
  - Elardo Presentation, undated
  - Scholarship Board- 1965
  - NYPO Art Awards- 1965
  - NYPO Art Winners- 1967
  - Turkey Winners- 1967/ Meeting- 1963
  - Goltz Scholarship Award- 1968
  - NYPO Prize Winner Photo- 8/1969, Aug 1969
  - Handicap Winner- 1969
  - Scholastic Winners- 1969
  - Elardo Family- 1/1970, Jan 1970
  - Elardo Family, undated
  - Scholarship Award, undated
  - World Fair Tix Raffle, undated
  - Post Master General J Lapenta receiving Elardo Award, undated
- Series XX: Classes/Seminars, XIII (Box 3)
  - Harry Kamish Fed Workshop- 1947-48, 1947-1948
  - Sen Javits and Pres MacKay Labor Studies College Teacher Training Institute-1961
  - Seminar at New School, undated
  - Delegates Seminars- 1968
  - Delegates Seminar, Union Office, undated
  - Community Classes- 1/1970, Jan 1970
- Series XXI: Workplaces, XIV (Box 3)
  - Brooklyn Army Terminal (BAT)- 3/1969, Mar 1969
  - Job-Mobile, Strahn Post Master- 1968
  - M-H on Job Training, undated
  - MVO- Pictures- 1969
  - Checking air pollution, work floor- 1964
  - Worksites, Miscellaneous, undated
  - Stations- 1969
- Series XXII: Union Office Staff, XV (Box 3)
  - J Ecker, Fin Sec and M Kanner, Sec, undated
  - Office Staff- 10/1959, Oct 1959
  - Union Offices- 12/1959, Dec 1959
  - Union at work- 12/1959, Dec 1959
  - Union Office- 3/1963, Mar 1963
  - Credit Union Office- 1965
  - Membership campaign- 1966
  - General Post Office Staff Retirees- 10/1969, Oct 1969
  - Checking 1187's, undated
  - M-B Office, undated
  - Office Staff: L Mitchell, undated
  - Maintenance, undated
  - NPU Health Plan, undated
  - Morley Kantor, undated
- Series XXIII: The Union Mail, XVI (Box 3)
  - Union Mail editor- Mgr editor- 1959
  - Editors Union Mail- 1967
  - Editing Union Mail- 1969
  - M Kanner, Union Mail, undated
  - Turkeys (Cartoon), undated
- Series XXIV: Sports/Recreation, XVII (Box 3)
  Arranged by sport and then chronologically.
  - Subseries A: Baseball
    - Baseball Champs- Morgan Station Team, Chelsea Park- 1963
    - Baseball Team- 1965 [see also Series 17-B: Folder 2 Softball Team-1965"]
    - Baseball Tournament, Chelsea Park- 1964 [see also Series 17-B: Folder 2 Softball Team-1965"]
    - Miscellaneous Baseball, undated
  - Subseries B: Softball
    - Softball Champs- 1963
    - Softball Team- 1965 [see also Series 17-A: Folder 2 Baseball Team- 1965"]
    - Softball Champs- 1965 [see also Series 17-A: Folder 4 Miscellaneous Baseball]
    - Opening Game Softball- 1968
    - Softball Champs- 1969
  - Subseries C: Basketball
    - Basketball Champs- 6/1964, Jun 1964
    - Basketball- 1964
    - Basketball- 1965
  - Subseries D: Bowling
    - Bowling- 1956
    - Bowling Season- 1957-58, 1957-1958
    - Bowling League Champs- 1958
    - Bowling Winners- 12/1959, Dec 1959
    - Bowling Season- 1963-64 (or 1965-66), 1963-1964
    - Bowling- 1964
    - Bowling, Madison Square- 1967-68, 1967-1968
    - Bowling- 1969-70, 1969-1970
  - Subseries E: Chess, E
    - Chess Club, M Siderman, VPGPO- 6/1963, Jun 1963
  - Subseries F: Handball, F
    - Handball Tourney- 6/1963, Jun 1963
    - Handball Champ, undated
  - Subseries G: Miscellaneous, G
    - Sports Awards- 7/1961
    - Sports Director W Boone, undated
- Series XXV: National Federation of Postal Clerks--Local 10 (New York), XVIII (Box 3)
  - National Federation of Postal Clerks- Local 10 (New York)- Events (ca 1953-1959)
  - Natl Fed of Postal Clerks- Local 10 (New York)-Portraits-Identified-Alphabetical, undated
  - Natl Fed Of Postal Clerks-Local 10 (New York)-Portraits-Unidentified, undated
- Series XXVI: Miscellaneous, XIV (Box 3)
  - Co-op City, Bronx- 11/1968, Nov 1968
  - Dolls in Hospital- 1959
  - General Post Office Fire- 1966
  - FDR Post office, model of proposed building, undated
  - Freedom National Bank, undated
  - Fowler, Rom (children) [see Series 19 Miscellaneous Negs], undated
  - Inquiring Editor, undated
  - Morgan Fire, undated
  - Union Recognition- 11/ 1961, Nov 1961
  - Misc, 1958
  - Misc, Identified, undated
  - Misc, Unidentified, undated
  - Misc, Unidentified, undated
  - A Ryland, E Bailey, undated
  - Negatives (ca 1970s) without matching contact sheets in the collection, 1970-1979
  - Miscellaneous contact sheets (ca1970s) possibly with matching negatives [see Series 19: Folder 17 Miscellaneous negatives, possibly with matching contact sheets], 1970-1979
  - Miscellaneous negatives (ca 1970s) that may have matching contact sheets in the collection (see Series 19: Folder 16, 1970-1979
  - Contact sheets (ca 1970s) that have matching negatives in the collection (Matching negatives may be found in Series 19, Folder 19: Miscellaneous negatives that have matching contact sheets in the collection), 1970-1979
  - Miscellaneous negatives (ca 1970s) that have matching contact sheets in the collection (Matching contact sheets may be found in Series 19, Folder 18: Miscellaneous contact sheets that have matching negatives in the collection), 1970-1979
- Series XXVII: 1996 Accession (Box 3, Box 4)
- Series XXVIII: Negatives, XX (Box 4, Box 5)